Guide to the Fritz Leiber Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Publications
  - Swords and Magic (Cover only) (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Swords and Ice Magic (Cover only) (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Swords Against Death (Cover only) (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Swords in the Mist (Cover only) (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Taboo - Lie Still, Snow White (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Tarzan and the Valley of Gold (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Thrilling Magazine - Power of the Puppets (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Thrilling Wonder Stories - The Foxholes of Mars (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Transmission - Repair People (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Two Sought Adventure (Dust jacket only) (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Unknown Worlds - The Hill and the Hole (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Venture Science Fiction - Demons of the Upper Air (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Vorpal Glass - My Love Affair with Witchcraft (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Weird Tales - Alice and the Allergy (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Weird Tales - The Automatic Pistol (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Weird Tales - Mr. Bauer and the Atoms (Box 42, Folder 33-34)
  - Weird Tales - In the X-ray (Box 42, Folder 35-36)
  - Whispers - The Button Molder (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Whispers - The Glove (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Wonder Woman - Introducing Fafhrd the Barbarian and the Gray Mouser (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - The World Fantasy Awards: Volume II - Terror, Mystery, Wonder (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - World's Best Science Fiction: 1966 - The Good New Days (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Worlds of IF - Science Fiction - Moon Duel (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Worlds of Tomorrow - Cyclops (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Worlds of Tomorrow - Sunk Without Trace (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - The Year's Best S-F - Mariana (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - You're All Alone - Four Ghosts in Hamlet (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Reviews
  Reviews of Fritz Leiber works, written by others. Filed alphabetically by story title.
  - Reviews (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - The Book of Fritz Leiber (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
  - The Big Time (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - The Change War (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Conjure Wife (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Fafhrd and the Gray Mouser (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Gather Darkness (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - The Ghost Light (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - The Knight and Knave of Swords (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - The Mind Specter - The Big Time (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Night Monsters (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Night of the Wolf (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Night's Black Agents (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Our Lady of Darkness (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - A Pail of Air (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Rime Isle (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - The Second Book of Fritz Leiber (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Ship of Shadows (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - The Silver Eggheads (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - A Specter is Haunting Texas (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Swords and Deviltry (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Swords of Lankhmar (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - The Wanderer (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - The World Fantasy Awards: Volume Two (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Reviews by Fritz Leiber
  Fritz Leiber's reviews of other authors' science fiction, fantasy, or literary works. This series is organized alphabetically by story title, if only the title is known, and by author, then title when the author is known.
  - Reviews by Leiber (Box 44, Folder 1-5)
  - Bread and Chocolate (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Comes a Horseman (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - The Cthulhu Mythos (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Curious Fragments: Jack London's Tales of Fantasy Fiction (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Emperor of Dreams (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Four Screenplays of Ingmar Bergman (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Hauntings (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - In Search of Ancient Astronomies (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Other Worlds 2 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Spirits of the Dead (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Star Trek (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Supernatural Cats, Etc. (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Survival Printout (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Year's Best Horror Stories: Series III (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Anderson, Poul - A Midsummer Tempest (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Bergman, Ingmar - The Magic Lantern, An Autobiography (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Bloch, Robert - Strange Eons (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Borges, Jorge Luis - Dr. Brodie's Report (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Bradbury, Ray - The Illustrated Man (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Burgess, Anthony - A Clockwork Orange (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Carter, Lin - Lovecraft: A Look Behind the "Cthulhu Mythos" (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - De Camp, L. Sprague - Literary Swordsmen and Sorcerers (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - De Camp, L. Sprague - Lovecraft: a Biography (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - De Camp, L. Sprague - Spirits, Stars, and Spells (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Ellison, Harlan - Angry Candy (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Ellison, Harlan - Deathbird Stories (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Ferris, Timothy - Galaxies (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Gorey, Edward (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Graham, Kenneth - The Wind in the Willows (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Grubb, David - The Siege of 318 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Hardy, Robin and Shaffer, Anthony - The Wicker Man (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Hawkey, Raymond - Wild Card (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Heinlein, Robert - I Will Fear No Evil (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Ibsen, Henrik - Peer Gynt (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - King, Stephen (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - King, Stephen - Cujo (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - King, Stephen - Danse Macabre (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - King, Stephen - The Dead Zone (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - King, Stephen - The Shining (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Lovecraft, H.P. - Selected Letters (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Lovecraft, H.P., et. al. - Watchers Out of Time, Etc. (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Lynn, Elizabeth - Watchtower (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Machen, Arthur - The Three Imposters (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Mann, Georg - The Dollar Diploma (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Mason, David - The Return of Kavin (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Milford, Nancy Winston - Zelda (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Niven, Larry - A World Out of Time (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Norman, John - Captive of Gor (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Ramsay, Raymond H. - No Longer on the Map (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Russ, Joanna - Picnic in Paradise (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Smith, Clark Ashton - Zothique (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Varley, John - Titan (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Walker, Dale L. - The Alien Worlds of Jack London (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Walton, Evangeline - The Sword is Forged (Box 44, Folder 59)
- Diaries/Daybooks, 1972-1989
  Fritz Leiber's spiral bound notebooks from 1972-1989, as well as several miscellaneous notebooks and sporadically filled out, undated diaries.
  - Diaries/Daybooks, 1972-1989 (Box 45-48)
- Biographical/Autobiographical Materials
  Interviews, bibliographies, biographical and autobiographical materials, genealogical items, clippings, about Fritz Leiber. Includes Fritz Leiber's obituary notices.
  - Interview (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
  - Bibliographies (Box 49, Folder 4-6)
  - Autobiographical summary (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Autobiographical materials (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Autobiographical materials - Introduction [?] (Box 49, Folder 9-10)
  - Autobiographical materials - World Authors (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Autobiographical materials - Galaxy (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Autobiographical notes (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Autobiographical photo captions [?] (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Autobiographical (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Biography notes (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Biographical notes (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Biographical materials - Quotes about Fritz Leiber (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Clippings about Fritz Leiber (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Obituaries (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Genealogy - Family tree (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Financial
  Tax returns, bills, canceled checks, check stubs, banking statements, and miscellaneous receipts.
  - California Tax Returns, 1971-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - California Tax Returns, 1977-1983 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Federal Tax Returns, 1966-1975 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Federal Tax Information, 1976-1989 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Federal Tax Information, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Taxes (Miscellaneous) (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Bills, Check Stubs, etc. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Receipts (Box 50, Folder 8-9)
  - Canceled Checks, Banking Statements (Box 51)
- Financial - Royalties/Remittance
  Royalty statements from various publishers for sales of Fritz Leiber works around the world. Arranged alphabetically by name of publishing house.
  - A.P. Watt (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Ace Books (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Ag-Az (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Ballantine Books (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Be-D (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - E-Gra (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Grosset & Dunlap, Inc. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - H-I (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - J-M (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - N-R (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - S-Z (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Legal
  Literary contracts and agreements filed alphabetically, copyright applications filed chronologically, estate papers for Fritz Leiber's first wife, aunt, and cousin as well as rental agreements and miscellaneous legal documents
  - Contracts/Agreements - A (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Contracts/Agreements - B (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Contracts/Agreements - C-E (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Contracts/Agreements - F-G (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Contracts/Agreements - H-M (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Contracts/Agreements - N-R (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Contracts/Agreements - S (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Contracts/Agreements - T (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Contracts/Agreements - U-Z (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Copyright registration (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Jury duty (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Rental agreements (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Leiber's estate (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Flora White' estate (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Ruth L. Williams estate (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Health/Medical
  Fritz Leiber's addiction rehabilitation documentation, notes on his eye surgery, as well as death certificate, funeral/cremation/memorial services arrangements.
  - Rehabilitation (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Rehabilitation/Therapy (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Eye Surgery (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
  - Death Certificate (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Cremation/Funeral Arrangements (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Memorial/Funeral Services (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Photographs
  Photographs and negatives of Fritz Leiber, his family, friends (identified and unidentified), and personal and professional activities.
  - Fritz Leiber (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - Fritz Leiber with Family/Relatives (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Fritz Leiber Appearances/Publicity (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Fritz Leiber and Unidentified People (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Jonquil Stephens Leiber (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Margo Skinner (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Bronson Leiber (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Justin Leiber, Casey Leiber (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Fritz Leiber, Sr. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Arlynn Leiber Presser (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Fischer Family (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Lynn Marron (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Identified Individuals (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Unidentified People (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Art (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Cats (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Seattle Convention (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Atlantic Highlands, New Jersey (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Pacific Palisades, CA (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Providence, RI (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Venice, CA (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Mt. St. Helens (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Small) (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Photos and Film Strips (Large) (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Illustrations/Artwork
  Artwork, photography, and illustrations of science fiction or fantasy topics. Very few of these pieces can be definitively linked to specific Fritz Leiber stories.
  - Photos - Burn, Witch, Burn (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Illustrations - The Ghost Light[?] (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Illustrations - The World of Nehwon (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Artwork - Operation Redemption (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Artwork - Polar Night (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Artwork - Sutro Tower (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - Model for The Wanderer (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Artwork - Worlds of IF (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Artwork - Yuggoth: The Pool (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Artwork - Yuggoth: Flight for the Third Planet (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Artwork - Yuggoth: Descent of the Star Spawn I (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Artwork - Yuggoth: Descent of the Star Spawn II (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Illustrations - Austin, Alicia - Erotica (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Artwork - Enzenbacher, Dale (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - Enzenbacher sculptures (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Artwork - Kirk, Tim (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Artwork - Kirk, Tim - Rime Isle (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Artwork - Krupp, Robin (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Artwork - Ostrom, Edison - Lathrop Crest (Leiber's stage name) (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Artwork - Schiff, Stuart David (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Illustrations - Sutherland, David - Lankhmar Game (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Artwork/Illustrations (Box 56, Folder 22-29)
- Convention Materials
  Flyers, programs, schedules, etc. of various science fiction and fantasy conventions Fritz Leiber either attended or was invited to attend. Filed alphabetically by the name of the convention.
  - [Philadelphia] (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - BAYCON (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Clarion-Milford (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - ConDome (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Conference for the Fantastic in the Arts (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Fantasy Conference (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Fantasy Faire (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Fantasy Worlds Festival (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Gen-con (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Houstoncon (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Iguanacon (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - International Conference on the Fantastic in the Arts (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - International Conference on the Fantastic in the Arts - 2nd (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - International Conference on the Fantastic in the Arts - 3rd (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - International Conference on the Fantastic in the Arts (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - International Conference on the Fantastic (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - LOSCON (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - MosCon (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - MunchCon (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Mystery Kon (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Nebula Awards (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - NECON (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Noreascon (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Norwescon (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Orycon (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - RHINOCON (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - A Science Fiction Fair (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Science Fiction Weekend (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - SEACON '79 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - SEACON '79 speech (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - SEACON (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Solarcon (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Unicon (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Westerchron 36 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Worldcon Scandinavia (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - 1st World Fantasy Convention (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - World Fantasy Convention (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - 4th World Fantasy Convention (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Worldcon (Boston bid) (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - 6th World Fantasy Convention (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - World Fantasy Convention (Box 57, Folder 41)
- Miscellaneous
  Materials in many different formats including publications with no Leiber material in them, awards/certificates, publishers' catalogs, clippings on various topics and items, and items relating to chess, theater, travel, and the University of Chicago. Publications are arranged alphabetically.
  - Miscellaneous Publications - A-LOCUS (Box 58, Folder 1-6)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Love-Z (Box 59, Folder 1-5)
  - Articles/Clippings - Movie/TV (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Articles/Clippings - Research (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Articles/Clippings - Science Fiction (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Articles/Clippings - Science (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Articles/Clippings - Authors (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Articles/Clippings - Theater/TV (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Articles/Clippings - Fringe elements (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Articles/Clippings - Travel (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Articles/Clippings - Fritz Leiber, Sr. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Articles/Clippings - Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Anti-war (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Awards/Certificates (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Catalogs (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Chess (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Flyers/Brochures/Programs (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - [Game?] (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Leiber, Justin - school report (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Mailing Lists (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Maps (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Mechanics' Institute (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Press Materials (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Publicity (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Tarot Cards (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Theater/Cinema (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Theater Programs (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Travel (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 3-7)
- Writings - Other Authors
  Manuscripts of other authors, including Harlan Ellison, Harry O. Fischer, Jonquil Stephens Leiber, Justin Leiber, Arlynn Patrick [Leiber], James Tucker, and Gene Wolfe.
  - Dubergey, Marie-Joseph and Philipe Bordier - Petite Planete de Vacances de Fritz Leiber (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Ellison, Harlan - Scartaris (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Evans, Deirdre (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
  - Evans, Deirdre - The Siren (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Fischer, Harry - The Childhood and Youth of the Gray Mouser (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Fischer, Harry - Recollections of Fritz Leiber (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Jakes, John - Fritz Leiber - An Appreciation (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens (Box 63, Folder 9-16)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - [Poetry] (Box 63, Folder 17-18)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - All By Herself (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Behold the Bride (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Dark Rendezvous (Box 63, Folder 21-23)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - The Doll House (Version II) (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Gammer Death at the Sill (Box 63, Folder 25-29)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Gimp and Go! (Box 63, Folder 30-31)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - The Heart's Desire (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Home Thoughts from Abroad (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Lo the Poor Bride (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Lord of Darkness (Box 64, Folder 4-8)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Love Have Rest (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - The Major's Crime - A True Story (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Mrs. Lansing (Proofs) (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Nada Court (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - The Nymph in the ??? (Box 64, Folder 13-18)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - One Against Hollywood (Box 64, Folder 19-20)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - The Paternity of Tom Jenkins (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - The Queer Woman (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - These United States (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - Talk of the Town (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Leiber, Jonquil Stephens - You Never Know, Do You? (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Leiber, Justin (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Leiber, Justin - Sword and Tower (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Leiber, Justin - Tit for Tat (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Leiber, Virginia Bronson - The Great Fritz (Box 65, Folder 4-6)
  - Patrick, Lynn - The Animal Noise, Princess with the Blue Paper Gown, The Second Bag from Dundalk, Shoetime (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Ramsay, Raymond H. - An Almanac of Eerie Beings (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Ramsay, Ray - Sample chapters 1-3 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Ramsay, Ray - Sample chapters 4-6 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Russell, David - Ghoulfest (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Slattery, Tom - Need Haunting Be So Lonely (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Spinrad, Norman - Destiny Times Three - Afterword (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Stephens, Emily - The Stranger's Glove (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Tomson, Sue - Trippy (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Trian, Chris - Secret Agent of the Wind (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - TSR Hobbies - Lankhmar Game (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Tucker, James - The Man in the Wall (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Wolfe, Gene - Quicks around the Zodiac - Afterword (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Writings - Unknown Authors
  - Bessie (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Forever and a Day (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - The Power of Suggestion (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - The Strange God (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - The Thing in the Lake (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Writings (Box 66, Folder 6-9)
  - Ch. 1 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 3 (Box 66, Folder 11-12)
  - Chapter 4 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Ch. 9 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 10 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Ch. 1: Delilah is Dead (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Ch. 2: Somebody Running on the Stairs (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Ch. 3: The House Next Door (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Ch. 4: No One Weeps (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Ch. 5: The Second Death (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Ch. 6: No One was There (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Ch. 7: The Third Death (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Ch. 8: The Webley Gun (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Ch. 9: The Confession (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Ch. 10: Motive! (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Ch. 11: The Face of the Stairs (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Ch. 12: The Bible Reader (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Ch. 13: The Murderer Returns (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Ch. 14: Many Things Explained (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Oversize Items
  - Oversize Art
    - Art, undated (Drawer F.7, Ovs folder 8)
    - Framed Items, undated (Ovs box 69)
  - Weaponry
    Two swords, not in boxes